#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ nguyenhoanganhcfo (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Strategic Business Development Commercial due diligence Business Transformation

#### Certifications

Critical Thinking
Learning Power BI Desktop

# Hoang-Anh Nguyen

Project Manager at Roland Berger

Ho Chi Minh City Metropolitan Area

# Summary

Experienced management consultant with a demonstrated history of working in investment and financial service industry. Expertise in M&A, Market Entry, Growth Strategy, Equity Valuation, Transaction Structure, Due Diligence, and Financial Analysis. Strong professional experience across Southeast Asia markets

# Experience

Roland Berger Project Manager September 2021 - Present (3 years 7 months) Vietnam

#### **KPMG** Vietnam

Manager

August 2019 - August 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Deal Sourcing | Commercial Due Diligence | Growth Strategy | Market Entry Advisory

BBTC Capital Partners Investment Manager 2018 - 2019 (1 year) Vietnam

Private Equity Investment focusing on renewable energy

### EY

Financial Due Diligence

January 2018 - December 2018 (1 year)

Düsseldorf, North Rhine-Westphalia, Germany

Financial Due Diligence

DHL Express
Business Performance Manager
2015 - 2016 (1 year)

Revenue and Sales Force Performance Management

Vietnam Asset Management Ltd Investment Analyst April 2012 - March 2014 (2 years) Equity Investment

## Education

The Philipp University of Marburg

Master of Science (M.Sc.), Economics · (2016 - 2018)

University Of Economics Ho Chi Minh City
Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.), Banking and Finance · (2008 - 2012)

VNU-HCM High School for the Gifted High School Diploma, Physics (2005 - 2008)